二零二二年滨州市初中学业水平考试。一，录音中有五个句子，听句子两遍后，从每小题三个选项中选出能对每个句子做出适。答语.
1. I hope everything goes well with you.
2. Could you please tell me where the teacher's office is?
3. Please turn off the light when you leave the room.
4. When was paper invented?
5. Jenny, I have a singing competition
我有唱歌比赛。这下午。二，录音中有。五组对话和五个问题，听对话和问题两遍后，从每小题三个选项中选出能回答所给问题的正确答案。
6. David, what about having some carrots for dinner?
7. David, what about having some carrots for dinner?
7. Did you see the robots in the museum yesterday?
Certainly, I saw some robots playing football.
How cool! Question, what were the robots doing?
8. Did 9.
What a nice picture!
It's a beautiful farm with cows everywhere.
10. I took the picture when I stayed in the countryside.
Question, what is the picture of?
11. Did you see in yesterday?
9. Here you are, I think you've made a mistake.
What I ordered is a cup of coffee, not juice.
Sorry, sir. Please wait a moment.
I'll get your drink soon.
Question, what did the man order?
Here you are, sir.
Oh, I think you've made a mistake.
What I ordered is a cup of coffee, not juice.
Sorry, sir. Please wait a moment.
I'll get your drink soon.
Question, what did the man order?
10. I'm sure that Jack's new house is somewhere on this street, but I don't know
exactly where it is.
I was told it is two blocks away from his old house.
Question, what are the two speakers probably doing?
10. I'm sure that Jack's new house is somewhere on this street, but I don't know
exactly where it is.
I was told it is two blocks away from his old house.
Question, what are the two speakers probably doing?
Question, what the doing?
录音中有一段对话和五个问题。听对话和问题两遍后，从每小题三个选项中选出能回答所给问题的正确答案。
the doing? Hello, this is speaking.
Hello, Tom. It's me, Joan.
I was sick at home today.
Did we get any homework today?
Well, we have to do the math exercises from 2A to 2F on page 30 in our textbook.
Sorry, from 2C, not 2A.
Alright. I got it.
Then we have to finish the reading list and write a report.
We have to hand it in by tomorrow afternoon, that's Thursday.
That's it for English.
Our history teacher wants us to read the first part of European history tonight.
Okay, I got all that.
Anything else? Oh, geography.
No, we haven't got any geography homework.
But our biology teacher wants us to look at a plant that we have at home and then be
ready to describe it tomorrow in class.
Wow, that's a lot of things to do.
Yeah. So, are you coming to school tomorrow?
Yes, I think so.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
See you. Hello.
This is Tom speaking.
Hello, Tom. It's me, Joan.
I was sick at home today.
Did we get any homework today?
Well, we have to do the math exercises from 2A to 2F on page 30 in our textbook.
Sorry, from 2C, not 2A.
Alright. I got it.
Then we have to finish the reading list and write a report.
We have to hand it in by tomorrow afternoon, that's Thursday.
That's it for English.
Our history teacher wants us to read the first part of European history tonight.
Okay, I got all that.
Anything else? Oh, geography.
No, we haven't got any geography homework.
But our biology teacher wants us to look at a plant that we have at home and then be
ready to describe it tomorrow in class.
Wow, that's a lot of things to do.
Yeah. So, are you coming to school tomorrow?
Yes, I think so.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
See you. Which math exercises does Joan have to finish?
12. What day is it today?
13. Which subject's homework does Joan not need to do?
Which subject's homework does Joan not need to do?
14. What will Joan do tomorrow?
15. What's the relationship between the speakers?
What's the relationship between the speakers?
四，录音中有一篇短文和五个问题。听短文和问题两遍后，从每小题
16. Which subject's homework Which Which subject's does not need
三个选项中选出能回答所给问题的正确。解答。
Which subject's Hello, boys and girls.
Today I am going to tell you something about health.
Health is the most important thing in the world.
How can we keep healthy?
Here are some suggestions for you.
First, we should eat healthily.
In order to eat healthily, I usually avoid eating food high in fat, like french
fries or cookies, which are junk foods.
I eat very little meat.
I eat a lot of vegetables and fresh fruit which are full of vitamins.
Second, exercising is very important.
Exercising every day helps us build a strong body.
You can play basketball or soccer.
As for your grandparents, they can do Tai Chi.
Third, I think friends are an important part of one's health.
I always feel better when I am with friends than when I am alone.
Happiness is also an important part of health.
It is good to spend time with my friends.
These things sound easy to do, but not everyone can manage them.
I think a strong will is necessary if we want to keep healthy.
I hope all of you will be healthy.
Hello, boys and girls.
Today I am going to tell you something about health.
Health is the most important thing in the world.
How can we keep healthy?
Here are some suggestions for you.
First, we should eat healthily.
In order to eat healthily, I usually avoid eating food high in fat, like french
fries or cookies, which are junk foods.
I eat very little meat.
I eat a lot of vegetables and fresh fruit which are full of vitamins.
Second, exercising is very important.
Exercising every day helps us build a strong body.
You can play basketball or soccer.
As for your grandparents, they can do Tai Chi.
Third, I think friends are an important part of one's health.
I always feel better when I am with friends than when I am alone.
Happiness is also an important part of health.
It is good to spend time with my friends.
These things sound easy to do, but not everyone can manage them.
I think a strong will is necessary if we want to keep healthy.
I hope all of you will be healthy.
Questions 16. How many suggestions are given by the speaker?
17. What kind of food does the speaker eat a
What kind of food does the speaker eat a
Which activity is good for the old?
19. Why should we spend time with our friends?
20. Which is not mentioned in the passage?
听力测试结束，请关注“锦鲤英语”微信公众号
21.